<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>C on Turio</title>
    <link>https://7und3dpy.github.io/website/tags/c/</link>
    <description>Recent content in C on Turio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://7und3dpy.github.io/website/tags/c/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 1: What is a pointer?</title>
      <link>https://7und3dpy.github.io/website/posts/pointerp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://7und3dpy.github.io/website/posts/pointerp1/</guid>
      <description>One of those things beginners in C find difficult is the concept of pointers. The purpose of this tutorial is to provide an introduction to pointers and their use to these beginners.
I have found that often the main reason beginners have a problem with pointers is that they have a weak or minimal feeling for variables, (as they are used in C). Thus we start with a discussion of C variables in general.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 2: Pointer types and Arrays</title>
      <link>https://7und3dpy.github.io/website/posts/pointerp2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://7und3dpy.github.io/website/posts/pointerp2/</guid>
      <description>Okay, let&amp;rsquo;s move on. Let us consider why we need to identify the type of variable that a pointer points to, as in:
int *ptr; One reason for doing this is so that later, once ptr &amp;ldquo;points to&amp;rdquo; something, if we write:
*ptr = 2; the compiler will know how many bytes to copy into that memory location pointed to by ptr. If ptr was declared as pointing to an integer, 4 bytes would be copied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER 3: Pointers and Strings</title>
      <link>https://7und3dpy.github.io/website/posts/pointerp3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://7und3dpy.github.io/website/posts/pointerp3/</guid>
      <description>The study of strings is useful to further tie in the relationship between pointers and arrays. It also makes it easy to illustrate how some of the standard C string functions can be implemented. Finally it illustrates how and when pointers can and should be passed to functions.
In C, strings are arrays of characters. This is not necessarily true in other languages. In BASIC, Pascal, Fortran and various other languages, a string has its own data type.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
